(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
またねーよ
See you later.
あー
Ahhh.
ニコニコ
Smiling.
あらあら
My, my.
はーふん
Hah-fun.
にゃあ
Nyaa.
ねむたい
I'm sleepy.
ちょこもねむたい
Choco is sleepy too.
ちょこー
Choco~
待て待て待て待て
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
お？
Oh?
にゃー！あはは
Nyaa! Ahahaha.
あーうー
Ah... uh...
ガチ？
Seriously?
やだやだやだやだ！
No, no, no, no!
どうもホロライブ2期生、悪魔とバーチャル保健医、癒月ちょこでーす。
Hello, I'm Yuzuki Choco, Hololive 2nd generation, a demon and virtual school nurse.
お前何言ってんだ！
What are you talking about!
うわぁー！
Waaah!
センキュースパチャ、センキューベリーマッチ。
Thank you for the Superchat, thank you very much.
ほら、豚。登って。頑張って、豚。
Look, you pigs. Climb up. Do your best, pigs.
ほら、豚。こっちよこっち。どっち？
Look, you pigs. Over here, over here. Which way?
はいはいはい。
Yes, yes, yes.
なんだろう？
I wonder what it is?
何年やってると思ってるんですか。えー？
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Eh?
先生に向かってなんですかその言葉遣いは！
What's with that tone of voice towards your teacher!
友達じゃないんですよ。いいですか？
We're not friends. You understand?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
It's Yuzuki Choco-sensei, after all!
あ、やばい。うわぁー！
Oh, crap. Waaah!
美味しかったの。
It was delicious.
あ、違う！
Ah, no!
だめ！あぁー！
Stop! Aaah!
ちょこしかおらん。
There's only Choco here.
なんか動いた！
Something moved!
なんだあいつ！
What's that guy?!
はい、いらっしゃいませー。
Yes, welcome.
どこ、行き先。
Where's the destination?
行き先、なー！
The destination, na-!
おやすみ。
Good night.
あーあー。
Ah, ah.
よし。
Alright.
はあ～、いい天気。
Haa~, such nice weather.
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい。
I want to take a nap in the nurse's office bed.
ずる休み　許されない
Skipping class, not allowed
保健室は神聖なの
The nurse's office is sacred
サボってる？　ちょっとだけ
Skipping? Just a little
誰も来なきゃやる気出ない
If no one comes, I have no motivation
チョコチョコ　センセーション　Yay！
Choco choco sensation Yay!
チョコチョコ　センセーション
Choco choco sensation
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
At this rate, I'll be hopeless
はあ、起きなきゃ　太るから
Haa, I gotta wake up or I'll get fat
二回目のあくび　おやすみなさい
A second yawn, good night
ごめんなさい　少しだけ
I'm sorry, just a little bit
寝かせて先生モード　シャットダウン
Let me sleep, teacher mode shutdown
夢見る　ふわふわ
Dreaming, fluffy
ずっとこうして眠りたい
I want to keep sleeping like this
ありがとう　ぽかぽか
Thank you, nice and warm
ちょっと休憩してるだけ
Just taking a little break
不意に君が来るなんて
For you to suddenly come here
ねえ、どこか悪いの？
Hey, is something wrong?
何かを期待しているのかな？
Are you expecting something?
揺らぐ心　巡る感情
Wavering heart, circling emotions
口どけ甘いセーショ
Sweet melting sensation
癒されたい　甘えたい
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled
構ってよチョコセンセーション
Pay attention to me, Choco-Sensation
君の視線　君の体温
Your gaze, your body temperature
分かっても恋は測れない
Even if I know them, love can't be measured
元気なのに　ため息しちゃう
Even though I'm healthy, I'm sighing
もしかして何かの病？
Could it be some kind of illness?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart pounds
ときめき運んで Step My You
So bring me excitement, Step My You
ずる休み　また来たの？
Skipping class again?
保健室は神聖なの
The nurse's office is sacred
サボってた？　ちょっとだけ
Was I napping? Just a little
やっぱり君にいて欲しい
After all, I want you to be here
明日は　週末
Tomorrow is the weekend
おやすみ…なんだよ！
Good night... wait!
居眠り　最高！
Napping is the best!
引きこもり　最高！
Staying indoors is the best!
もちろん　ノーメイク
Of course, no makeup
休みだったら白衣脱ぎます！
If it's a day off, I'm taking off the white coat!
さあ全てを見せて
Come, show me everything
シャープに判断できないじゃん
I can't judge sharply, can I?
何を隠してるの？
What are you hiding?
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
I can hear the speed of your heartbeat
見せて心　捲るシャツを
Show me your heart, unbuttoning your shirt
正常保てるテンション
A tension that stays normal
愛されたい　頼られたい
I want to be loved, I want to be relied on
構ってよチョコセンセーション
Pay attention to me, Choco-Sensation
君の重み　君の匂い
Your weight, your scent
分かっても愛は測れない
Even if I know them, love can't be measured
大好きだから　ため息しちゃう
Because I love you, I'm sighing
やっぱりそれは恋の病
It really is love sickness
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart pounds
ときめき運んで Step My You
So bring me excitement, Step My You
混ざり合った　この世界だって
Even in this mixed-up world
みんな癒しが　必要だから
Because everyone needs healing
チョコチョコ　センセーション　Yay！
Choco choco sensation Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you too
揺らぐ心 巡る感情 口どけ甘いセセーション
A swaying heart, circling emotions, a melt-in-your-mouth sweet sensation
癒されたい 甘えていたい よってよチョコセセーション
Wanting to be healed, wanting to be spoiled, come closer, Choco sensation
君の視線 君の体温 分かっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your warmth, even if I understand them, love can't be measured
元気なのに ダメージしちゃう もしかしてもう手遅れ
I'm healthy, yet I'm taking damage, maybe it's already too late
でもドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて マイシューデイズ
But I can't move until my heart thumps, so bring me that spark, My Shoe Days
チョコチョコセセーション イェイ！
Choco Choco Sensation, yay!
絶対君をダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you rotten
はい！ということで！
Yes! And so!
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026、始まりましたー！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 has begun!
見て見て！
Look, look!
1曲目から、ちょこ、生まれ変わりました！
From the very first song, Choco has been reborn!
いや今日はね、原点回帰ということで
Today, it's a return to my roots,
ちょこの、なんと保健室ステージなの！
featuring Choco's very own infirmary room stage!
いやちょっと保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって
The infirmary room has also been reborn a bit
めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりました！
and it's become super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとかできそうだよね。
It feels like we could do situation dramas here.
今日は生まれ変わったニューちょこと
Today, with the reborn New Choco
素敵なね、ゲスト様をいっぱい呼んでライブをしていくんだけど
I'll be performing a live show with many wonderful guests,
その前に
but before that...
みんなちょこのこと、もっと見たいよね？
Everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あー、でもまだダメだよ。
Ah, but not just yet.
これから来るお二人に、ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいました！
I've asked the two coming up next to hold a photo session for Choco!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう。
So, let's call them out right away.
ノエル様！ラミィ様！
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
ちょこし！
Choco-shi!
せーの！
One, two!
ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとう！
Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
えーということで今回はね
So, for this time,
この可愛い両手に花で
with these cute flowers on both sides,
可愛いお二人に、ちょっとね、ちょこの撮影会をしてってもらおうと思うんですけど
I'm going to have these two cute people do a photo session of Choco.
まずは自己紹介、よろしくお願いします。ノエちゃんから！
But first, please introduce yourselves. Starting with Noe-chan!
はい！えー、こんまっする！
Yes! Um, Konmuscle!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと、
I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Generation!
はい！
Yes!
ホロライブ5期生の顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
And I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive 5th Generation, whose face is a liver!
今日はおねがいしまーす！
Thank you for having us today!
まあね、ちょっとちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところを
Well, Choco-sensei's points that have become really cute...
ちょっと団長頑張って、攻めていこうと思いますのでよろしくお願いします。
this Knight Commander will work hard and try to push the limits, so look forward to it.
攻めちゃって攻めちゃって！
Go ahead and push it, push it!
ラミィも攻めるよね？
Lamy, you're going to push it too, right?
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy also wants to push it to the very edge!
いや撮影会やるならちょっとね、この二人を呼ぶしかないかなって思って、呼んじゃいました！
I thought I had no choice but to call these two if I were to do a photo session!
嬉しい！
So happy!
いやしかもしかも
And furthermore...
ちょっと後でこの3人から
later on, from the three of us,
なんとお知らせもあるみたいなので
there seems to be an announcement,
お知らせなんだー！気になる！
An announcement! I'm curious!
まあ撮影会の後で、皆様楽しみにしててくださーい。
so everyone, please look forward to it after the photo session.
楽しみだーい！
I'm looking forward to it!
それじゃあちょっと、こちらで撮影会よろしくお願いします！
Then, let's start the photo session over here!
はーい！行くぜー！
Yes! Let's go!
お、なんかすごいとこ来たぞ。
Oh, we've come to an amazing place.
ねえ、すごい！可愛い！
Hey, amazing! Cute!
可愛いでしょう、可愛いでしょう。
Cute, right? It's cute, isn't it?
撮影会はちょこのここの診察室でやりまーす！
The photo session will be held here in Choco's examination room!
イェーイ！診察しちゃうぞ！
Yay! I'm going to examine you!
可愛い！
So cute!
ね、可愛い！
Right? So cute!
でしょう、でしょう！
Right, right?!
でもさ、診察室だけど...
But wait, this is a clinic, but...
ベッドは？ベッドどこ？
Where's the bed? Where is it?
あれ？あ、本当だ。
Oh? Ah, you're right.
なんかパネルもあれ？
What's with that panel too?
あれ使う？
Are we using that?
あ、チョコ、それダメ！
Ah, Choco, not that!
え、これダメなの？
Eh, I can't use this?
そこは本編で使うの。
That's for the main part of the stream.
あ、何？
Ah, what?
そっか、本編か！
Oh, right, the main part!
ちょっとね、ベッドとか、ちょっといろいろ...
Well, you know, with the bed and stuff...
撮影会とか、シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって...
I was thinking of doing a photo session and a situation drama...
シチュエーションドラマ！
A situation drama!
とんでもないことしようとしてる！
She's planning something crazy!
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
まあね、それは置いておいて。
Well, setting that aside for now.
今回は、二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので。
I want you two to take some photos of me today.
まずは...
First...
分かりました！
Understood!
撮りますよ、よいしょ。
Let's take some photos. There we go.
ラミィ様には、こちら！
For Lamy-sama, this!
本格的な！すごいカメラ来た！
A professional one! A great camera is here!
そして、ノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, this one. Ta-da!
なんだいこれ？
What is this?
チョコのギリギリを守るために、特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
It's a mosaic stick specially made to protect Choco's 'edge'!
特別すぎる！すごいの来た、モザイク！
That's too special! Something amazing came, a mosaic!
ボタンで、このモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい！
Apparently, you can change the intensity of the mosaic with a button!
今めっちゃ粗くなってるから。
It's really coarse right now.
あ、本当だ、薄くできる！本当だ！
Ah, you're right, it can be made thinner! It's true!
すげえ、でも粗いほうがむしろいいまである、これ。
Amazing, but the coarse one might even be better.
確かに。オッケー、隠すよ！
True. Okay, I'll hide it!
これ大丈夫かな、でも配信ね、ちょっと守りますよ。
Is this okay? I'll protect the stream though.
チョコの配信を守ってください！頑張ります！
Please protect Choco's stream! I'll do my best!
それでは、撮影会スタート！イエーイ！
Now, let's start the photo session! Yay!
まずはやっぱり全身。
First, a full-body shot as expected.
そうだね、そうだよね。
Right, definitely.
普通に、こうね、ポーズ、いつものチョコ先の。
Normally, like this, the usual Choco-sen pose.
あー！美しい、うわー！
Ah! Beautiful, wow!
美しい！あー、いいいい、いいよ！
Beautiful! Ah, good, good, that's it!
可愛い！もうここちょっとまずいんじゃない？これ。
So cute! Isn't this already a bit risky?
まずいかな？あ、逆に、逆に！
Is it bad? Ah, on the contrary, on the contrary!
ちょっと待って、ノリノリなんですけど！
Wait a second, she's really into it!
まずいかな？ちょっとね。
Is it bad? Just a little.
ここ、揺れて、モザイクが！モザイクが追いついてない！
It's shaking here, the mosaic! The mosaic can't keep up!
ノエル様、頑張って頑張って！
Noel-sama, hang in there, hang in there!
こうやってね、こういう感じで、うんうん。
Like this, in this way, yeah, yeah.
ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてもいいですか？
Can you try jumping for a bit?
ジャンプ、確かに。すごい、プルッ...
Jumping, true. Amazing, wobble...
あ、やばい！めっちゃ揺れてる、あかん、あかん、これ！
Ah, no! It's shaking so much, no, no, this is bad!
ちょっとせっかくだから、椅子とかも座っちゃう？
Since we're at it, why don't you sit on the chair?
椅子ね、ここにありますね。はーい、よいしょ。
The chair, it's right here. Okay, there we go.
あ、いいいね！靴も可愛い！
Ah, nice! The shoes are cute too!
なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。
It looks a bit bluish.
そう、チョコね、そこが赤なの。
Yeah, for Choco, that part is red.
えー！あ、ちょっと、ま、ま...
Eh! Ah, wait, m-m...
まずい、ありがとうございます！
Risky, thank you very much!
そこがね、赤なの、これ。ありがとうございます！
That part is red, you see. Thank you very much!
大丈夫、あ、でも中見えてないからね。大丈夫です。
It's okay, ah, but nothing's visible inside. It's okay.
セーフです！守ってます、チャンネル守ってます！
Safe! I'm protecting it, protecting the channel!
じゃあ、こう、どんどん、どんどん、上を見てもらって。
Then, let's gradually look at the upper body.
あ、いいいね！あ、可愛い！
Ah, nice! Ah, so cute!
見えてる？見えてるよ、見えてるよ！うん。
Can you see? I can see, I can see! Yeah.
見えてる？あ、可愛い！可愛いね、おー！
Can you see? Ah, so cute! You're cute, oh!
え、ちなみにラミィさん、あれですよ。
Eh, by the way, Lamy-san, there's that.
この椅子に座って先生ポーズも、あ、先生ポーズ！
Sitting on this chair for a teacher pose... Ah, teacher pose!
撮ってほしい、先生ポーズ。
I want a photo of the teacher pose.
先生ポーズって何だ？こんな感じ？
What's a teacher pose? Like this?
あー、いい！いいですね、いい、非常にいい！
Ah, nice! It's good, very good!
これもうモザイクいらないね、これは。非常に、非常に。
We don't need the mosaic for this. Very, very nice.
本当にいらないのか、これ？いや、わかんない、わかんない。
Do we really not need it? Well, I don't know, I don't know.
チョコ先の魅力が溢れすぎてて、いいですね！
Choco-sen's charm is overflowing, it's great!
素晴らしい！え、じゃあ団長もいいですか？何、何？
Wonderful! Eh, then is it okay for Dancho too? What, what?
お尻フリフリをちょっと、していただきたいんで。
I'd like you to do a little hip wiggle.
フリフリ、えーと、そう、後ろ向いてもらって。
Wiggle, um, yeah, turn around please.
白衣越しだけど。フリフリ、あ、いいね、フリフリ！
Even through the white coat. Wiggle, ah, nice, wiggle!
白衣越しだが、その下に、あ、ちょっと、その下に！
It's through the white coat, but underneath... Ah, wait, underneath!
スカート結構際どい！でもこれ、うん、白衣ってこれ...
The skirt is quite risky! But this, yeah, the white coat...
脱げ、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
Take it off, I want you to take it off, but can't you?
脱げるけど、本編でって言ってた。
I can, but I said that's for the main part.
あ、本編なら脱いでくれるんですね！あー！
Ah, so you'll take it off in the main part! Ah!
ガニ股、あのココ会長リスペクトで、ガニ股好きなんで。
The bow-legged pose, out of respect for Coco-kaicho, I like it.
はい！ガニ股ー！いいいね！
Yes! Bow-legged pose! Nice!
ガニ股助かる！ガニ股ー！
Bow-legged pose is a lifesaver! Bow-legged!
これちょっとモザイク、モザイク！あ、見えてるもん、あ！
A little mosaic here, mosaic! Ah, something's visible, ah!
モザイクお願いします！モザイクが、無効か！
Mosaic please! Is the mosaic ineffective?!
逆にやばい！やばい、やばい、やばい、やばい！
On the contrary, it's bad! Bad, bad, bad, bad!
可愛い、ふうー。どんどんいこう、どんどんいこう。
Cute, whew. Let's keep going, keep going.
じゃあ、ラストはやっぱりアイドルだからさ、チョコ先。
Then, for the last one, since you're an idol, Choco-sen.
アイドル、とびきり可愛いアイドルお願いします！
An idol, please show us your most adorable idol pose!
はい！え、可愛い！
Yes! Eh, so cute!
いやこれ、あ、いいいね！フフフ。
No, this... ah, nice! Hehehe.
可愛い！
So cute!
おっ！
Oh!
アップいい！顔のアップいいわね！
The close-up is good! The close-up of your face is great!
たまらんです！
It's irresistible!
可愛い！
Cute!
オッケー！
Okay!
いっぱいいただいた！
We got plenty of photos!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうー！
いや、ちょっとね、この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので...
Well, we'll be continuing this in the members-only stream...
♡このあとのメン限♡
アフターライブ　特別撮影会
シチュエーションドラマ2本
♡Upcoming Members-Only Stream♡
After-Live, Special Photo Session
2 Situation Dramas
メン限ではちょっと、歌も撮影会も、
In the members-only stream, we'll have a song, a photo session,
シチュエーションドラマも、なんと2本やっちゃいます！
and even two situation dramas!
おー！楽しみだ！
Oh! Looking forward to it!
え、ちなみにさ、なんかタイトルとかあんの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, do those situation dramas have titles?
あ、今回のタイトルが...
Ah, the titles this time are...
先生と...
With Teacher...
ベッドで特別バレンタイン！
A Special Valentine in Bed!
あー！特別！
Ah! Special!
たまらん！
Irresistible!
先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン！
Special Valentine with teacher in bed!
ってタイトルと、あと...
That's one title, and also...
「診察室で甘い処方箋を」っていう...
"A Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room"...
♡シチュエーションドラマ♡
先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン
診察室で甘い処方箋を
♡Situation Dramas♡
A Special Valentine in Bed with Teacher
A Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room
えー！あまーい！
No way! So sweet!
あまーい！
So sweet!
最高すぎる！
That's just the best!
あの、目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて...
Um, for the POV, we're having the cameraman lie on the bed...
ちょっと、みんなが本当に、あの、本当に見えるように、
So that everyone can really, um, really see,
チョコが覆いかぶさるように、ちょっと、あは！
I'll be leaning over you... haha!
おおー！たまらん！
Ooh! Irresistible!
見たい！
I want to see!
いろんな画角で撮っていきたいと思います！
I'd like to film it from various angles!
えー、楽しみ！
Oh, can't wait!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ということでそろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います！
And with that, we're running out of time, so let's get back to the live performance!
こんな気持ちでね...
With these feelings...
ライブだった！
It was time for the live!
そうだ！
That's right!
急げ！
Hurry!
急げ、急げ！
Hurry, hurry!
それでは聴いてください。
Now then, please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
とろとろその身をベイビー
Melting, that body baby
溶けちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Melt away and catch me darling
ふわふわココアふわり
Fluffy, cocoa lightly
ゆるゆる　ワンツー
Loose, one two
なんか眠れない夜には
On nights when I can't somehow sleep
お散歩　特別なパーティータイム
A walk, a special party time
２人きり　やった！
Just the two of us, yay!
あの角曲がれば
If we turn that corner
ベンチしかない公園だよ
It's a park with only benches
蒸し暑い空気の中
In the humid air
迷い込むんだ
We wander in
コンビニちょっと寄り道
A little detour to the convenience store
買い出しアイスじゃなくって
Buying more, not ice cream
これがいい
This is better
缶のお酒ほろ酔い
Canned alcohol, feeling tipsy
ウインクでストロング
Strong with a wink
リキュールじゃもう酔えない
Can't get drunk on liqueur anymore
ラムで潰してお願い
Please knock me out with rum
お砂糖多めマシマシで
With extra sugar, more and more
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ溶かして
Melt it in the scorching heat
ゴクって飲んで
Take a gulp
癖のある私のことを
Treat me, with all my quirks
大事にしてよね
With care, okay?
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
とろとろその身をベイビー
Melting, that body baby
溶けちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Melt away and catch me darling
ふわふわココアふわり
Fluffy, cocoa lightly
ゆるゆる　ワンツー
Loose, one two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely way home
ふらふら特別なボーナスタイム
Dizzy, a special bonus time
手を繋ごう　イェイイェイ！
Let's hold hands, yay yay!
大きめTシャツ
An oversized T-shirt
君に借りたありがとうって
Saying "thank you" for borrowing it from you
寝癖みたいにして
Looking like I just woke up
困らせたいんだ
I want to trouble you
コンビニまた寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しいもう一本だけ
Having fun, just one more bottle
弱いやつ
Of the weak stuff
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ゆるゆるに解けるテンパリングが大事
It's important to temper it so it melts smoothly.
熱すぎても飽きちゃって冷たいのはダメよ多分
Too hot and I'll lose interest, and cold is probably no good either.
チョコみたいな私をプレシャスに扱ってみて
Try treating me, just like chocolate, as something precious.
炭酸のお酒でシュワシュワシュワ
Fizzy, fizzy with carbonated drinks.
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない 恋してるチョコみたいでした
Love won't reach if you don't express it; I'm in love, and it's just like chocolate.
チュッとして
Give it a kiss.
夜空のグラスにキラキラこぼして
Spilling sparkles into a glass of the night sky.
息もできないくらいにほら立ってだって恋に溺れて
Look, I'm so deep in love I can barely breathe.
君の熱で溶けたらそのまま食べてよ
Once I melt from your warmth, eat me right then and there.
手にベトベトついちゃって 一生一緒
Getting all sticky on your hands, let's be together for a lifetime.
甘濃いお酒ほろ酔い ウインクでストロング
Sweet, rich alcohol, a bit tipsy, making it "Strong" with a wink.
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラブで尽くして お願い
I can't get drunk on just liqueur anymore; please, serve me with love.
お砂糖マシマシで飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra helpings of sugar; I don't care about it being easy to drink.
灼熱でさ溶かして ごくって飲んで
Melt it with scorching heat and gulp it down.
癖のある私だからさ 君が選ばれたサマーチョコレート
Since I'm quite the handful, you're the one chosen for this Summer Chocolate.
ドロドロトロりベイベー 溶けちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Melting and gooey, baby; I'm melting away, so catch me, darling.
ピュアピュアココアふわり ゆるゆるワンツー！
Soft, pure cocoa; loosely, one, two!
What's up Japan! Can you hear me? It's Reggaeton style!
No money, no job, too much problems! We have no reason to be sad! It's time to get up!
We have a hot new song! That's from AKB48!
To make you feel good! Fortune Cookie! So dance Japan crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie in Love
作詞：秋元 康 / 作曲：伊藤心太郎
Lyrics: Yasushi Akimoto / Composition: Shintaro Ito
あなたのことが好きなのに
Even though I'm in love with you,
私にまるで興味ない
You don't seem to have any interest in me at all.
何度目かの失恋の準備 Yeah Yeah Yeah
Getting ready for yet another heartbreak, yeah, yeah, yeah.
まわりを見れば大勢の
Looking around, I see so many
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
Other cute girls everywhere.
地味な花は気づいてくれない Yeah Yeah Yeah
You never notice a plain little flower like me, yeah, yeah, yeah.
カフェテリアに流れるMusic ぼんやり聴いていたら
While listening aimlessly to the music in the cafeteria,
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ つま先から動き出す
Before I know it, I'm moving to the rhythm, starting from my toes.
止められない今の気持ち
I can't hold back these feelings anymore.
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー 占ってよ
Come on, come on, come on, come on, baby, tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie in Love!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't looking all that bad.
Hey Hey Hey
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To bring good luck your way, you've got to show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
A Fortune Cookie for the heart!
運勢 今日よりも良くしよう
Let's make our luck even better than it is today.
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
Life isn't so bad after all, is it? A miracle that'll blow you away is going to happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling that somewhere, we'll fall in love.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie in Love
あなたにちゃんと告りたい
I want to confess to you properly
だけど自分に自信ない
But I have no confidence in myself
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can imagine your reaction
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いい子がいいなんて
"A girl with a good personality is better,"
男の子は言うけど
That's what boys say, but...
ルックスがアドバンテージ
Looks are an advantage
いつだって可愛い子が
Always the cute girls
人気投票1位になる
Get first place in the popularity poll
Please please please oh baby
私も見て
Look at me too
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie in Love
その殻さあ壊してみよう
Come on, let's try breaking that shell
Hey hey hey
先の展開神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know what happens next
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie of Tears
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative
Hey hey hey
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is overflowing with love
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
It makes you forget sad things
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
I think tomorrow the wind will blow for tomorrow
Come on come on come on come on baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie in Love
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't that bad
Hey hey hey
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To call for luck, show a smile
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune Cookie of the Heart
運勢今日よりも良くしよう
Let's make our luck better than today
Hey hey hey
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't so bad after all
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
A feeling that I can love you somewhere
君が好きったら君が好き
If I say I like you, I like you
ピュアラ ピュアラ ピュアラ ピュアラ ラブ...
Pure Pure Pure Pure Love...
初恋大戦争
First Love Great War
作詞・作曲：Medansy (TRIPFONTiER)　編曲：Yo-SK
Lyrics/Composition: Medansy (TRIPFONTiER) Arrangement: Yo-SK
あのね乙女は本気出すと凄いんです
Hey, a maiden is amazing when she's serious
1 2 いずれ手中に あの手この手で
1 2, eventually in my hand, with this and that trick
ライバルを出し抜くの
Outsmarting the rivals
全部計算済み レシピ通り
Everything is calculated, according to the recipe
好きだって武器にして
Using "I like you" as a weapon
嘘吐いてみたりして
Trying to tell lies
酔ったフリで甘えて
Spoiling by pretending to be drunk
すでに出来上がり
Already finished
うわっ出遅れた
Whoops, I'm late
つまみ食いしたら無くなった
I ate it all while snacking
恨んでや日本酒
Be resentful, sake
時にファンキー
Sometimes funky
苦いのはNGで
Bitter is no good
女の子の季節だもん
It's a girl's season
全部思い通りになってよね
Let everything go exactly as I want
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied with me
本命あげちゃう メルシー
I'll give you my favorite, Merci
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war I won't give to anyone
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
My heart flutters, Merci
それじゃ手繋いじゃう内緒のデート
Then let's hold hands, a secret date
スウィーティ スウィーティ キス
Sweetie sweetie kiss
甘くていいの
Sweet is fine
スウィーティ スウィーティ ハート
Sweetie sweetie heart
濃いのがいいっしょ
Deep/thick is better, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's my first love
絶対譲らない覚悟です
I'm prepared to never give up
本気なのです
I'm serious
目を見て言って 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and say your feelings
ピュアラ ピュアラ ピュアラ ピュアラ ラブ...
Pure Pure Pure Pure Love...
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battle field
誰これと喋ってんの
Who is this talking to?
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battle field
西へ東へ奔走
Running west and east
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battle field
大丈夫へこたれないもん
It's okay, I won't give up
惚れさせたが勝ちです
The one who makes the other fall in love wins
鼻血出そう 食べちゃいな
I'm about to have a nosebleed, eat it
砂糖の量は愛の量
The amount of sugar is the amount of love
間違えた これ塩だった
I made a mistake, this was salt
マボランシン
Maboranshin
強気強気してはいる
I'm acting tough
真心こめてラッピング
Wrapping it with all my heart
自分も本気モードで行く
I'm going into serious mode too
祈るラッキーチャンス
Praying for a lucky chance
何度も試作した
I've tried many times,
横練習もした
and practiced my side-talk too.
夜明けにあとなるな
Don't let the dawn come just yet.
大丈夫 自分史上
It's okay, because I'm the
一番可愛い私なんだから
cutest version of myself ever.
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied with me.
結ばれる運命なのです
It is our destiny to be tied together.
本命あげちゃう メルティくん
I'll give you my heart, Melty-kun.
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
A great war I won't lose to anyone.
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
I'm throbbing, Merci.
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃい 内緒のデート
Then let's hold hands, it's a secret date.
チュキチュキキ 甘くていいな
Love-love-love, it's so sweet.
チュキチュキハ こういうのが一番
Love-love-love, this is the best.
初恋なんだもん
Because it's first love.
絶対譲らない 覚悟です
I'm determined not to give in.
本気なのです
I'm serious.
目を見て言って 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me your feelings.
ピュアラ ピュアラ
Pure-la Pure-la
ピュアラブ
Pure Love
はーい！ということで、チョコたち3人の新曲でした！
Yes! So, that was a new song by the three of us!
イエーイ！
Yay!
新曲でしたー！改めまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にね
It was a new song! Once again, this is a new song
コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど
called "First Love War" that I sang with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama.
今回作詞作曲をめんま様、そして
This time, we asked Menma-sama for lyrics and composition,
編曲を楊慶様にお願いいたしました
and Yokei-sama for the arrangement.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いや、今回のテーマが、バレンタインの日に
Well, the theme this time is that on Valentine's Day,
3人の可愛い女の子たちが1人の男の子を手に入れるために
three cute girls try to outsmart each other
バチバチにね、出し抜こうとするみたいな
fiercely to get one boy...
なるほど
I see.
激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております
It's a super sweet theme song.
いいね。可愛い
Nice. Cute.
そう。いやもう、3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので
Yes. Since our three voices combined to make it a great idol song,
ぜひぜひ皆様聴いてください
please listen to it, everyone.
聴いてね！
Please listen!
えー、何回も聴きたいな
Eh, I want to listen to it many times.
ねー、何回も聴きたいよね
Right, we want to listen many times.
沼る、逃げるところとかあるのかな？
I wonder if there's any part to get hooked or lost in?
いや、こちらの楽曲は、このあと24時から、2月の15日0時からね
Well, this song will be starting from 24:00 today, 0:00 on February 15th,
各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
distributed on various music sites!
やったー！聴ける！
Yay! We can listen!
じわじわ。そしてね、え？この配信後すぐに
And then, eh? Right after this distribution,
この楽曲の……MVが！
the MV of this song will be...!
やったー！公開されます！
Yay! Released!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いや、ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聴いて、MVの方にもちょっと感想とかね
I'd be happy if everyone listens to it a lot and leaves some feedback
コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなーって思います
or comments on the MV.
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
じゃあね、2人とも今日はありがとう
Well, thank you both for today.
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ああ、ありがとう！嬉しい
Ah, thank you! I'm happy.
引き続きね、頑張ってください
Please keep doing your best.
頑張ってね！頑張る！ありがとう！
Good luck! We will! Thank you!
ほんならば、ちょっと、おさらばじゃ
Then, well, farewell.
おさらばじゃ！おさらば！
Farewell! Farewell!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そしてここからライブ後半となります
And from here, it will be the second half of the live.
まだまだゲストパートとか、なんと最後に重大告知もあるので
There are still guest parts and, surprisingly, a major announcement at the end,
皆様一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
so let's enjoy it together, everyone!
それでは、次のゲストはこちら！
Now, the next guest is here!
大人なフリして
Pretending to be an adult.
大人なフリして。
作詞・作曲：s-num
Pretending to be an adult.
Lyrics & Composition: s-num
急に会いたいって
Suddenly saying you want to meet,
いつものように準備してる
I'm preparing as usual.
午前1時すぎの終電で向かうって返した
I replied that I'd take the last train after 1 AM.
やめときなよって言われても
Even if I'm told to stop,
また会いに行く
I'll go see you again,
会いたいから
because I want to.
別れ際に落ち合う
Meeting up when it's time to say goodbye
街の風は少し冷たい
The city breeze is a bit chilly
慣れないワイン無理矢理飲み干してしまっては
Forcing down wine I'm not used to drinking
ふらふら
I'm feeling dizzy
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手しちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess things up?
少しも見逃したくない
I don't want to miss a single thing
ちょっと期待してね
Have a little expectation, okay?
ずっと見栄張ってね
Keep putting up a front, okay?
周りばかり気にして生きてる
I live my life constantly worrying about others
ちょっと優越感でも
Even if it's just a little sense of superiority
なんか寂しくて
I somehow feel lonely
本当は自分じゃない気がして
I feel like I'm not truly myself
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Forcing myself when it's not like that at all
味のしないキスをしても
Even if we share a tasteless kiss
やっぱり一番嬉しくて
It's still what makes me the happiest
取り繕った私は可愛いのかな
Am I cute even when I'm just keeping up appearances?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I break
今にも切れそうな
Connected by a thread
糸で繋がってる恋だね
That feels like it's about to snap at any moment
私が諦めたらきっと
If I were to give up, I'm sure
簡単に消えちゃうね
It would simply vanish
引き止めるにはどうする
What should I do to make you stay?
あの子だったらどうする
What would that girl do?
不器用な指先絡めて
Entwining my clumsy fingertips
いつもチェックしてね
Always keep an eye on me, okay?
息苦しくてね
It's suffocating, you know?
他の子と比べてばかりいた
I was constantly comparing myself to other girls
一番見てほしい
I want you to look at me most of all
目の前のあなたは
Yet you're standing right in front of me
どこか違う景色見てる
Gazing at a different scenery somewhere
いつも優しいふりして
Always pretending to be kind
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
Smiling even though it's not like that
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get
孤独はどこか充満して
The more the loneliness fills the air
少しずつ離れていくのがわかるよ
I can feel us slowly drifting apart
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I forget everything
自分がもっと強ければさよならを
If I were a bit stronger,
言えるのにね
I'd be able to say goodbye, wouldn't I?
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Forcing myself when it's not like that at all
ふと見せる優しさが
The kindness you suddenly show
ずっと忘れられなくて
Is something I can never forget
取り繕った私は可愛いのかな
Am I cute even when I'm just keeping up appearances?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I break
そしてこぼれ出した愛は
And then, the love that overflowed—
私頑張ったよね
I really did my best, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてねと
Hoping that you'd look my way someday,
思っていたもういいから
I thought... but that's enough now
取り繕った私は中へとゆく
My made-up self is retreating inside
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I forget everything
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You somehow always look sleepy,
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
And you somehow always look bored,
なんかいつもやばそうだし
And you somehow always look like you're in trouble,
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
And you're somehow always on your phone,
本当はテンション高いのに
Even though you're usually high-energy,
私といる時だけ低いし
It's only low when you're with me,
なんなん自分ありえなくない？
Seriously, what's up with you? Isn't that messed up?
キライ 大キライ どうでもいい！
I hate you, I really hate you! I don't care anymore!
だったら僕も言うけどさ
Well, if you're gonna say that, I've got things to say too.
小さい事ですごく怒るし
You get mad over the smallest things,
いっぱいいっぱいすぐ泣くし
And you're quick to start crying when you're overwhelmed,
ごめんって言っても許してくれないし
And you won't forgive me even when I say sorry,
そのわり急に飽きちゃえば
But on top of that, if you suddenly get bored,
ケッタはよ帰るとか言うし
You'll just say you're taking your bike home early,
あーなんて罪深き人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are,
ちくしょう もう知らんぞ
Dammit, I'm done with you!
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love is
口どけ味の秘密のチョコレート
A secret chocolate with a melt-in-your-mouth flavor
二人で
The two of us—
二人だけのデコレーションを
Decoration just for the two of us
ちりばめて彩って
scattered and colored
食べちゃおうか
Shall we eat it?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
Mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If you warm it and mix it, surely
いつかお口に合う味になるの
it'll eventually become a taste that suits your mouth
ねぇねぇ、チョコいいかな
Hey, hey, can I talk to you, Choco?
なんで？
Why?
さっきは、あのね、ごめんね
About earlier, um, I'm sorry
何が？
For what?
いつも、モヤってなるじゃん
I always get all hazy, right?
それで？
And?
今日は、これを渡したくて
Today, I wanted to give you this
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Words aren't enough, you see
だから？
So?
受け取ってくれないかな？
Would you please accept it?
何よ？
What is it?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me
わぁぁ！
Waaa!
なんだよ、それ！
What's with that?!
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃう
I end up depending on your kindness
誰よりも近いから 素直になれない
Because we're closer than anyone, I can't be honest
君の一生懸命さ ついつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting how hard you try
誰よりも一番 大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone else
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure box of dreams
奇跡味の代償のチョコレート
Chocolate as the price of a miracle flavor
二人だけのイノベーションを
Innovation just for the two of us
探し組み立てたら賑やか
If we find it and build it, it'll be lively
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter makeup box of daily life
世界味の代償のチョコレート
Chocolate as the price of a world flavor
冷め切って割れないように
So it doesn't cool down and break
大事に包んで生涯の完成まで
Wrapping it carefully until the completion of a lifetime
いつだって
Always
病める時も
Even when sick
どんな時も
No matter when
そうずっと
Yes, forever
健やかな時も
Even when healthy
手を取って 違う二人を分かつまで
Taking hands, until the different two are parted
愛してる
I love you
僕もそうさ
So do I
そばにいて
Stay by my side
そばにいる
I'll stay by your side
なんて嘘かもよ
That might be a lie
ああそうかい 僕も適当に言った
Ah, I see. I just said it randomly too
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet
苦い苦い
Bitter, bitter
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
Secret chocolate with the taste of the universe
二人だけのデコレーションを
Decoration just for the two of us
ちりばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
scattered and colored, shall we eat it?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
Mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたら絶対
If you warm it and mix it, absolutely
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
it'll eventually become a taste of supreme happiness
Thank you so much! See you next time!
ねぇ、ひとつだけ
Hey, just one thing...
聞いてもいい？
Can I ask you?
私のことを
About me...
告白日和、です！
Confession Day, it is!
会えるかな今日は 心が騒いで
Will I meet you today? My heart is restless
ズキズキしたくなる 時めき踊る瞬間
It starts to ache, the moment my heart dances
私のことなど 多分気にしてないの
You probably don't even care about me
だけどここにいるんだよ 私はここよ
But I'm right here, I'm right here
地面が揺れ動く 嫌われてないかな
The ground is shaking, I wonder if you hate me
勢いでとにかく 挨拶だ
With momentum, I'll just say hello
やっと晴れたね
It finally cleared up
ぱっと晴れたね
It suddenly cleared up
そして元気になれ
And then, cheer up!
「おはよう」の代わりに
Instead of "Good morning"
背中をたたいて さあ行くよ
I'll pat your back, here we go!
やっと晴れたら
Once it finally clears up
ぱっと晴れたら
Once it suddenly clears up
きっと元気な笑顔
Surely, a cheerful smile
なんだか今のこの 気持ちが切なくなったよ
Somehow, this current feeling has become painful
授業は上の空 遠くを眺めたい
Daydreaming during class, I want to look far away
恋って甘いもんじゃない 違うかもださ半分
Love isn't a sweet thing, or maybe it is, half and half
目に見るだけでいい
Just looking with my eyes is enough
触って確かめなきゃ分からないから
Because I won't know unless I touch and make sure
動き出そうよ　自分らしくね
Let's start moving, in our own way
楽しく生きるの
Live happily
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle
言わずに悔やむより勇気出そう
Better to have courage than to regret without saying it
ずっと前から　うんと前から聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you for a long, long time
私から最初に伝えてしまえ　大好き
Let me be the first to tell you, I love you
ずっと前からだよ　うんと前からだよ聞いたことに答えて
It's been a long, long time. Answer what I asked
どんな風に感じてるの？全部見せてよ
How are you feeling? Show me everything
楽しく生きるの
Live happily
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle
本当は不安でも勇気出そう
Even if I'm actually anxious, let's have courage
出そう？
Let's?
うん！
Yeah!
ずっと前から　うんと前から聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you for a long, long time
私から最初に伝えてしまえ　大好き
Let me be the first to tell you, I love you
ずっと前からだよ　うんと前からだよ聞いたことに答えて
It's been a long, long time. Answer what I asked
どんな風に感じてるの？全部見せてよ
How are you feeling? Show me everything
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces through the chest
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you
ねえ
Hey
教えて
Tell me
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔
A little regret over words that passed each other by
涙こぼれて
Tears overflow
忙しい感情鼓動にリンクする
Busy emotions link with my heartbeat
チューニング
Tuning
確かめたいんだ
I want to make sure
目的ばっかりとらわれて
Getting caught up only in the goal
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
Important things become hazy and run away
今日もリスタート
Restart again today
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces through the chest
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything
ねえ
Hey
聞かせて
Let me hear
たった1ミリが遠くて
Even just one millimeter is far
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I ran through
忘れない忘れられない
Won't forget, can't forget
輝く1ページ
A shining page
お似合いの二人になんだか複雑な気持ちがいるよ
I have somewhat complicated feelings about the matching pair
初めての感情鼓動にリンクする
First-time emotions link with my heartbeat
体温計
Thermometer
...こぼれちゃったかな
...Has it spilled over?
自分のことは分からないまま
Without even understanding myself,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even went and gave her advice.
胸が痛いや
My chest hurts.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
気づいたこの想いは
These feelings I've realized,
もう遅いの
It's already too late.
あの子の方が可愛いの
She's cuter than me,
知ってるよ だけど
I know that, but...
「うまくいかないで」なんて
"I hope it doesn't work out,"
逃げ出したいクセに
Even though I want to run away from such thoughts.
ちょこ、君のこと全部知りたいって思っちゃう。
Choco finds herself wanting to know everything about you.
これが恋だって初めて気づいたの。
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい。
I definitely want you to look my way.
遅かったけど... 諦めたくない！
I'm late, but... I don't want to give up!
だって... 好きだから！
Because... I love you!
春に咲いた花が恋をした
The flowers that bloomed in spring fell in love.
花は必死に上を向いて笑った
The flowers looked up and laughed with all their might.
青い夏の蕾も恋をした
The buds of the blue summer also fell in love.
咲かない花と火薬の匂い
A flower that doesn't bloom and the scent of gunpowder.
本当の気持ち言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words,
大事なこと話せたら
If only I could talk about what's important.
今日もリスタート
Today is another restart.
どんなどんな君だから
Because it's you, whatever kind of person you are,
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you right now.
ねえ...
Hey...
好きです
I love you.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
全部分かり合いたいよ
I want us to understand everything about each other.
ねえ 聞かせて
Hey, let me hear it.
たぐり寄せて もう0センチ
Pulling you close, now there's zero centimeters between us.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days we ran through,
忘れない 忘れられない 輝く1ページ
I won't forget, I can't forget, this shining page of my life.
はい！ということで！
All right! So!
ここまではアキ様、ロボ子、ござるに、はあとと一緒に歌わせていただきました！
Up until now, I sang along with Aki-sama, Roboco, Gozaru, and Haato!
みんなありがとうー！
Thank you everyone!
さてさて、ここからはなんと重大告知が２つあります！
Now then, from here on out, there are two major announcements!
まず１つ目が...こちら！ドドン！
First, the first one is... this! *Drumroll*
癒月ちょこ 誕生日記念 2026グッズ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to introduce them to you in more detail.
まずはこちら！ちょこのクッション！
First up is this! Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね、いやちょっとちょこの誕生日といえば... 毎年Nardack先生ありがとうございますということで...
You know, when it comes to Choco's birthday... I always have to thank Nardack-sensei, so...
今年もNardack先生にめちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
This year again, Nardack-sensei drew an incredibly wonderful illustration for me!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで... ちょこめいとを抱きながら...
This time the theme is Valentine's... so I'm hugging a Chocomate...
ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
This time, I decided to make it a chocolate-style cushion!
可愛いでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので...
The size is just about right for a pillow...
ちょっとねお昼寝の時とか仮眠用に、つやーってできる感じで使えちゃいます。
So you can use it to drift off into a nice sleep during a nap or a quick rest.
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
なんと！
And look!
今回初めてちょっとね お菓子が作れる
For the first time ever, something you can use for baking...
なんと なんと ちょこのチョコレート型！
It's Choco's very own chocolate mold!
耐熱も 冷却も あったかいのも 冷たいのも
It's both heat and cold resistant, so hot or cold,
両方使えちゃって
you can use it for both.
ちょっとね ショコラと チョコメイトの
今回は チョコレート型になっております。
This time, it's a chocolate mold featuring
Chocolat and the Choco-mates.
まあ マフィンとかね クッキーとか
Well, you can make muffins, cookies...
あとはまあ 普通に 冷やし固めて チョコレート入れたりとか
or just simply chill some chocolate inside.
なんか いろいろ使えるから ぜひ みんなも作ってみてね。
It has many uses, so please try making something!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
お待たせしました！
ちょこの すやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Thanks for waiting!
Choco's Zzz Plushie Keychain!
まあ ちょこと言えばね 睡眠ということで
Well, sleep is synonymous with Choco,
超ロングスリーパーのちょこが 今回は
ぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって ちょっと すやすやぬいぐるみで
作らせていただきました。
so as a super long sleeper, I decided to
make this sleeping plushie keychain.
まあ ずっとね 肌身離さず持っていれば
いつか ぐーって聞こえてくるかも しれない。
If you always keep it close to you, you might
eventually hear a snoring sound.
そして 今年もございます。
癒月ちょこ 書き下ろし台本の 耳舐め ASMR 台本！
And we have it again this year.
A lip-licking ASMR scenario written by Yuzuki Choco!
撮りましたよ ちょこの ASMR ボイス。
今回ね 耳舐めの方は 3つございます。
I've recorded Choco's ASMR voices.
This time, there are three lip-licking scenarios.
1つ目が 「お出かけのチョコレート」。
The first one is "The Chocolate of Your Outing."
いや こちらはね ちょっと あの 皆様がご想像してるより
ちょっと あの あの エチチかもしれないんですけど...
Now, this one might be a bit more... seductive
than you might imagine...
まあ 配信ではね 絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので
ぜひともね 皆様 ご購入して聞いてみてください。
It's a voice pack that I absolutely couldn't do on stream,
so please buy it and give it a listen.
そして もう1つが 「残業後のご褒美デザート」ということで
こちらはね ちょことの同棲シチュエーションとなっております。
And another one is "Residual Overtime Reward Dessert,"
which is a cohabitation situation with Choco.
はい。ちょこが 残業してきて 帰ってきた時の...
Yes. When Choco comes home after working overtime...
うーん まあデザートは ちょこなの か 君なの か
どっちなんだろうね。
Hmm, I wonder if the dessert is Choco or you?
まあ ちょっと聞いてみてよ。そしてそして
「年下幼馴染の ツンデレバレンタイン」ということで
Well, just listen to it. And then, there's
"The Tsundere Valentine of Your Younger Childhood Friend."
今回はね 聞いている君たちが ちょっと
隣の家の お兄ちゃんになった気分で 聞いてみてください。
For this one, please listen as if you're the big brother
who lives next door.
こちらもね 耳舐めボイスとなっておりますが なんと こちら
ド M の方は 絶対に聞いていただけたら
ちょっと ニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います。
This is also a lip-licking voice pack, and I think
masochists will definitely find themselves
smiling while listening.
はい。そしてそして フルセットをご購入の方
フルセット特典 今回はなんと 初めて チェキ風ブロマイドカードに
なりました。
And finally, for those who buy the full set,
the bonus item is a polaroid-style card
for the first time ever!
ちょっと こちらね 数量限定で
直筆サイン & 箔押し複製メッセージが 入っております。
カキカキしちゃうよ。
The limited edition comes with a handwritten signature
and a foil-stamped printed message.
I'll be writing them out!
通常バージョンは 箔押し複製サインと
複製メッセージが 入ります。
The regular version includes a foil-stamped signature
and a printed message.
そしてね 特典がもう1つ！ フルセット購入特典として
「焼きもちの ぎゅー」 と ASMR ボイスが入っております。
And there's one more bonus!
As a full set purchase perk, you get the "Jealous Hug"
ASMR voice pack.
いや こちらはね ちょっと あの 甘々の ぎゅーボイスなので
まあちょっとね 普段あまり ちょこ嫉妬しないんですけど
ちょっと まあ 何に嫉妬してるかは 聞いてからのお楽しみなんですけど
It's a very sweet hugging voice pack. I don't
usually get jealous, so you'll have to find out
what I'm jealous of by listening!
ちょっと ぜひぜひ ニヤニヤしながら聞いておいてください。
ぜひ手に入れてください。
Please enjoy listening to it with a grin on your face.
Be sure to get it!
そしてそして 重大告知 2つ目は こちら！
And now, for the second major announcement!
「…ねえ、ちょこたち もう二度と会えないの？」
"...Hey, Choco... will we never see each other again?"
不思議ねキミの言葉を聞くと なんだか元気が出てきちゃう。
It's strange, hearing your words... I somehow feel energized.
ちょこのことをもっともっと、大好きになってほしい。
I want you to love Choco more and more.
もう一度、会いたいよ。
I want to see you once more.
ちょこが小悪魔なのは…
The reason why Choco is a succubus...
ねえ、もしよければキミに……ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしい。
Hey, if it's okay with you... I want you to hear Choco's memories.
「The Beginning」
12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース & 連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
"The Beginning"
12-month consecutive original song releases & linked voice drama project start
3/15 から毎月15日の0時 オリジナル楽曲リリース
Original song release on the 15th of every month at 0:00, starting 3/15
豪華アーティスト参加
Gorgeous artists participating
癒月ちょことあなたのストーリーを辿った 全12話のボイスドラマ
A 12-episode voice drama following the story of Yuzuki Choco and you
「The Beginning」project 始動！
"The Beginning" project starting!
はい！ というわけで
Yes! And so...
えー、癒月ちょこ、
Um, Yuzuki Choco...
12ヶ月連続オリ曲リリースが決定しましたー！
has decided to release original songs for 12 consecutive months!
The Beginning
2月15日からオリジナル楽曲12曲連続リリース
楽曲に連動したストーリーのボイスドラマ発売
豪華アーティストが参加
The Beginning
Original song release for 12 consecutive months starting Feb 15th
Release of story voice dramas linked to the songs
Featuring gorgeous artists
しかもこちら、なんとオリ曲に
And what's more, for these original songs,
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが一緒にリリースされます。
voice dramas linked to the story will be released together.
いや、こちらね、約1話から12話まで
So, from episode 1 to episode 12,
1曲ずつに連動してボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててください。
there's a voice drama linked to each song, so please look forward to it.
そして今回はね、その記念すべき1曲目をこれから披露したいと思います。
And today, I'm going to perform that memorable first song.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
『キミの秒針』
'Your Second Hand'
戻れないから また
Since I can't go back, again
あなた 愛しさが募る
you, my love for you grows
キミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you
キミの秒針
作詞：マズ(vivi) | 作曲：御薬袋楯(vivi)
Your Second Hand
Lyrics: Mazu (vivi) | Composition: Shitate Minai (vivi)
キミから受け取った 壊れそうなストーリー
The fragile story I received from you
どこまでも広がる 仰いだ空
The sky I looked up at, spreading endlessly
変わらない毎日も 色のない夢も
Unchanging days, colorless dreams too
手放して 始めようよ
Let's let go and start
不安の夜を数え
Counting anxious nights
泣きながら迎えた 明日でもいい
Even if it's a tomorrow I welcomed while crying
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I spread the memories I've carved out
戻れないから また 愛しさが募る
Since I can't go back, again my love for you grows
キミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you
二人で温めた 大切なストーリー
The precious story the two of us nurtured
遠くまで続いた 果てない道
The endless road that stretched far away
疲れたら代わるから そう言ってくれた
'I'll take over if you're tired,' you said
優しさに触れて見えた
Touching your kindness, I could see
受け入れてくれたこと
That you accepted me
忘れない 嬉しくて満ちた日々
I won't forget the days filled with joy
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain
架かった虹のように綺麗な
Beautiful like a rainbow stretching across
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Each and every word from you
今も 宝物
Is still a treasure now
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me
輝ける この気持ち届けよう
I'll deliver these shining feelings
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I spread the memories I've carved out
戻れないから また 愛しさが募る
Since I can't go back, again my love for you grows
キミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain
架かった虹のように綺麗な
Beautiful like a rainbow stretching across
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Each and every word from you
今も 宝物
Is still a treasure now
はい！ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Hi! So, how was it everyone?
今回の新曲「キミの秒針」は...
My new song, "Kimi no Byoushin" (Your Second Hand)...
しどの真央様が作詞、そして二目組あつし様が作曲、編曲、
...is written by Mao Shito-sama, and composed and arranged by Atsushi Nimegumi-sama,
そして編曲にはなんと加藤貴之様も加わっていただきました！
and Takayuki Kato-sama even joined us for the arrangement!
いや、今回は、ボイスドラマ連動企画の第一弾として...
Well, this time, as the first part of a voice drama tie-in project...
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような書き下ろしの楽曲に仕上がっております。
...it's a newly written song that serves as the theme song for the entire story.
まあドラマの鍵となるね、秒針というメタファーにも要注目してください。
Please pay close attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which is the key to the drama.
しどさんだけではなく、
Not only Shito-san,
このあとね、豪華アーティストの皆様にもたくさん書いていただいたので...
many wonderful artists wrote for me after this as well...
皆様リリースをお楽しみに！
so everyone, please look forward to the release!
こちらの「キミの秒針」は各音楽サイトは...
This song "Kimi no Byoushin" will be on music sites...
ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます。
...and while there's a bit of a gap, it's scheduled for release on March 15th at midnight.
まあちょっとね、公開まで時間があくから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してみてください。
Since there's some time until the release, please watch this stream many times until then.
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it carefully!
そしてそして、
And also,
MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので楽しみに待っててくださーい！
the MV will also be released at a later date, so please look forward to it!
ということで、今日のチョコの生誕ライブはどうだったかなー？
So, how was Choco's birthday live today?
まあこのあとは、すぐに、
Well, immediately after this,
冒頭、最初の方でお披露目した、
the one we showed at the very beginning...
ノエルちゃんとラミィたんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があって、
...the MV for "Hatsukoi Daisensou" by the three of us with Noel-chan and Lamy-tan will be released.
そのあとメン限で、
After that, in the membership-only stream,
ちょっとライブと撮影会の続きとか、ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れない...
we'll have the continuation of the live and photo session, and something you can only see in membership...
シチュエーションドラマとかやるので、ぜひぜひ気になる人は見に行ってくださーい！
...like a situation drama, so if you're interested, please come watch it!
それではまた後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, let's meet again later!
おつかれーと！
Otsu-kare-to!
はむっ、ちゅっ！
*Ham, Chu!*